WSYR Collection
WSYR Collection
- Audiorecordings
  - President Truman special message to Congress, part 1 of 3; President Truman at University of California, part 2 of 2, 06/12/1948; 07/27/1948; wsyr_radio_055; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 9)
    Side A: Controlling inflation, high prices and housing shortage; Side B - closes with short piece of music - a march
  - President Truman special message to special session of Congress, parts 1 and 3, 11/17/1947; wsyr_radio_056; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 10)
  - President Truman speech - Syracuse, 10/16/1952; wsyr_radio_408; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman speech, part 3; Molotov and translation of Molotov’s speech; President Truman first speech, part 1, 04/17/1945; 04/26/1945; wsyr_radio_063; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 5)
    A-President Truman speech (Part 3), radio address closes with NBC chimes; Foregn Commisar Molotov speech, conclusion and and translation in English, San Francisco conference; B- President Truman first speech before Congress (part 1). Pressident Truman encloses President Roosevlet. Pressident Truman discusses war time
  - President Truman speech; [unknown], 03/06/1952; wsyr_radio_399; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman talk (part 1), 07/13/1949; wsyr_radio_361; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman talk (part 2), 07/13/1949; wsyr_radio_362; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman talk on O. P. A. (part 1); Shell digest, 06/29/1946; wsyr_radio_308; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman talk on O. P. A., Part 2 (#11), 06/29/1946; wsyr_radio_309; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman to Greece and Turkey (part 1); Goes calling on Mrs. Breuman, Mattydale (part 1, program 77), 03/12/1947; wsyr_radio_327; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman, M. G., parts 1 and 2, 06/14/1952; 06/19/1952; wsyr_radio_044; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 8)
    A-President Truman address: Keel Laying ceremonies for the first atomic powered submarine "The Nautilus". Q. T. H. - electric boat division, General Dynamics Corporation Submarine yard, Groton Connecticut
  - President Truman, Part 1 of 2, wsyr_radio_293; label damaged; Lacquer discs/acetates
    President Truman, Part 1 of 2 - Address profiteering - meat storage e "General stabilization program", from NBC network at White House, Price regulation Congress, O. P. A., ?/14/1946
  - President Truman’s Airfield dedication to General Hap Arnold, 06/25/1951; wsyr_radio_384; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman’s Farewell Address, 04/12/1945; 01/16/1953; wsyr_radio_085; note on label reads: "Start on Apr. 12th, 1945, end - That war my 1st [?]". UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 13)
  - President Truman’s speech on the removal of General MacArthur as Far East commander (parts 1 and 2), 04/11/1951; wsyr_radio_380; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prime Minister Attlee (part 1 and 3), 11/13/1945; wsyr_radio_268; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prime Minister Attlee (part 1); R. C. A. Show - Music America loves best; Roy Rogers (part 2), 10/26/1945; 11/04/1945; 11/09/1945; wsyr_radio_264; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prime Minister Attlee (part 2 and 4), 11/09/1945; wsyr_radio_265; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prime Minister Attlee (part 2); Governor Thomas Dewey at Cornell University, 11/12/1945; 11/13/1945; wsyr_radio_269; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prime Minister Attlee (part 3), 11/09/1945; wsyr_radio_266; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prime Minister Churchill (part 2 and 4), 05/19/1943; wsyr_radio_196; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prime Minister Churchill (part 2 and 4), 03/21/1943; wsyr_radio_210; note on label reads: "Carton #10"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prime Minister Churchill (part 2 and 4); "D Day" Prayer with President Roosevelt, 03/26/1944; 06/06/1944; wsyr_radio_221; On side 2 note reads: " Chuel [sic] "When the signal is given Almighty god. End on sens.: will triup [sic]"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prime Minister Churchill (parts 1 and 3), 05/19/1943; wsyr_radio_195; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prime Minister Churchill (parts 1 and 3), 03/26/1944; wsyr_radio_220; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prime Minister Churchill, part 2; Olivio Santoro, [Boy Yodeler], 11/29/1942; wsyr_radio_016; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 2)
    B- "Modern Cannon ball", sung to tune of "Wabash Cannonball"; "I've got wings on my Bronco in the sky"; "I get the neck of the chiken", Bobby Hookey; Trivio: Pet food spot and Jingle
  - Prime Minister Winston Churchill in Quebec, part 2; Secretary Cordell Hull, part 1, 08/31/1943; 11/10/1943; wsyr_radio_025; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 3)
    B- 1: Moscow Conference report to Congress
  - Punch Lines From Speeches on War By World Leaders: [Benito] Mussolini (Dec. 7 - Dec. 11); [Franklin] Roosevelt; That They Might Live, part 1, wsyr_radio_031; SIDE B UNPLAYABLE NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 4)
    Punch Lines From Speeches on War By World Leaders: [Benito] Mussolini (Dec. 7 - Dec. 11); [Franklin] Roosevelt; That They Might Live (Part 1); Enlistment of volunteer nurses aids
  - Punch Lines From Speeches on War By World Leaders: Neville Chamberlain, parts 1 and 2; Winston Churchill - Fall of France; That They Might Live, Program 44, part 2, wsyr_radio_032; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 4)
    A-That They Might Live, Program 44 (part 2), script by James Hart, score and conducted by Boris Momorsky [?], starring Binnie Barnes
  - Queen Elizabeth coronation oath, Westminster Abbey; Elizabeth II Coronation (actual), 06/02/1953; wsyr_radio_412; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Queen Elizabeth’s Coronation speech, Churchill introduction and actual Crowning of Queen Elizabeth (finale), 06/02/1953; wsyr_radio_411; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Queen Mary eulogy (Grandmother England), 03/29/1953; wsyr_radio_082; script by Joseph Denbow, speaker for NBC, George Hiks. Side A only.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 12)
  - R.F.D. Aircheck - Don Daver (reel 3), 06/07/1972; wsyr_radio_495; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 15)
  - Radio and Television Department O. C. C. Special Lincoln’s Birthday Program, 1977; wsyr_radio_920; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 10:38 (Box 52)
  - Radio Talk, MidniteTalk on TV (DeBernardis, ER Vadeboncoeur and [Alan] Milair). Various Cuts, 09/12/1955; 09/15/1955; wsyr_radio_039; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 7)
    A-1: DeBernardis Radio talk; 2: Television talk, 12 midnight, part 1; B-1: Television talk, 12 midnight, part 2; 2: E. R. Vadeboncoeur talk on television. Paul C. DeBernardis running for local traffic Court Justice. Side B -1, part 2 of Television talk 12 Midnight is UNPLAYABLE, NOT TRANSFERRED.
  - Raymond Gram Swing; Wendell Willkie speech (part 2); ESSO and Rusterholtz (part 2), 02/12/1941; 02/13/1941; 02/17/1941; wsyr_radio_155; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Religion Makes News, 07/25/1971; wsyr_radio_900; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 14:26 (Box 50)
  - Remembrance Day - General [Jonathan Mayhew] Wainwright (parts 2 and 4), 09/23/1945; wsyr_radio_280; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Rev. Rasberry/ Gospel Sound, 03/07/1976; 03/15/1981; wsyr_radio_895; includes additional information in box; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 32:00 (Box 50)
  - Rev. Rasberry/ Gospel Sound, 03/12/1978; 03/07/1982; wsyr_radio_896; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 32:00 (Box 50)
  - Rev. Rasberry/ Gospel Sound, 03/21/1976; 03/22/1981; 01/05 [no year]; wsyr_radio_897; includes Music Clearance Sheet in box; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
  - Reverend Rasberry and Gospel Sound, PB, Mormon Tabernacle Choir, 12/27/1981; wsyr_radio_571; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 22:10 (Box 21)
  - Reverend Rasberry and Gospel Sound, PB., 11/14/1981; wsyr_radio_568; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:25 (Box 21)
  - Reverend Rasberry and Gospel Sound, PB., 11/21/1981; wsyr_radio_569; 1/4 inch audio cassette; running time 23:00 (Box 21)
  - Reverend Rasberry and Gospel Sound, PB., 12/13/1981; wsyr_radio_570; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 24:00 (Box 21)
  - Reverend Rasberry and Gospel Sound, PB., 01/17/1982; wsyr_radio_572; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Reverend Rasberry and Gospel Sound, PB., 02/14/1982; wsyr_radio_573; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:00 (Box 21)
  - Reverend Rasberry; Gospel Sound, 03/14/1976; wsyr_radio_539; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - RFD Deacon Tribute - Original - (part 2), wsyr_radio_467; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 57:34 (Box 12)
  - RFD Deacon Tribute - Original (part 1), wsyr_radio_466; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 61:01 (Box 12)
  - Richard Nixon Speech re: Eisenhower Administration, 04/23/1953; wsyr_radio_101; B - UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 15)
  - Robert Bockman for Congress Committee, wsyr_radio_1001; note on box reads: "Bockman original-Dub, (1-30; 2-30). Two 30 sec spots to be rotated - Don Shart, TA 384; 541."; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 1:00 (Box 58)
  - Rocky Horror Show, sound effects, 09/27/1984; wsyr_radio_624; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Rosemary Pooler for State Senate, 09/25/1980; wsyr_radio_1031; Four 60-second commercials; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 4:00 (Box 59)
  - Sales tax funeral (ER Vadeboncoeur), 02/28/1950; wsyr_radio_048; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 8)
    A-Vadeboncouer: Views the News - Unions Repeal of Syracuse Sales Tax Law. Sponsor - P. Lorillard Tobacco Company; Spots for "Old gold cigarettes" and Briggs Pipe mixture, Elliot Gove announcer; B-outtake from above (low level)
  - San Francisco Conference, Foreign Commissar Molotov speech (all in Russian), part 2; President Truman first address before Congress, part 2, 04/16/1945; 04/26/1945; wsyr_radio_060; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 5)
  - San Francisco United Conference, part 3; Translation of Molotov speech; Foreign Minister Eden of Great Britain, part 1, 04/26/1945; wsyr_radio_061; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 5)
  - Scoreboard, wsyr_radio_557; call-in sports questions show; includes portions of commercials, lots of talk about Coach Maloney, PSAs; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 65:00 (Box 20)
  - Secretary [of the Navy Frank] Knox (part 2); President Roosevelt - Address Canadian Parliament (part 1), 08/25/1943; 08/28/1943; wsyr_radio_194; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Secretary Cordell Hull, part 2; [second side is illegible], 11/18/1943; 3/22/1944; wsyr_radio_030; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 4)
    A-Secretary Cordell Hull address (part 2); B-1: Multitreiency toner; B-2: "Hit and win", quiz show (part 2). B-2: Daily 9:35-10 AM, Jimmy Vincorl and his Orchestra, M. C. - Bob Rowly, Small orchestra plays "Caravan", Duke Ellington composition. WSYR program - "You forgot to remember" is sung by Dick Moore with orchestra
  - Secretary John Foster Dulles - cabinet meeting, parts 1 and 2, 10/25/1954; wsyr_radio_097; first broadcast of a Cabinet session combined radio and television networks and newsreel White House, Q. T. H., closes with "Stars and Stripes Forever".; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 15)
  - Secretary of State [Edward] Stettinius, Jr., 03/05/1945; wsyr_radio_259; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Secretary of State Marshall on Moscow conference (part 1); Syracuse Speaks (part 2), 04/26/1947; 04/28/1947; wsyr_radio_329; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Secretary of State Marshall on Moscow conference (part 2); [unknown], 04/28/1947; wsyr_radio_330; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Senate Spotlight - [Alfonse] D’Amato, 10/27/1985; wsyr_radio_583; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Senate Spotlight - [Alfonse] D’Amato, wsyr_radio_584; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Shoplifting interview Woman’s World, wsyr_radio_588; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
    11/29 - Syracuse Chamber of Commerce, Monty Houston - project Smash; 12/12 - Syracuse Chamber of Commerce, Monty Houston - project Smash; 12/19 - Syracuse Chamber of Commerce - project Smash, Preston Delaski - president of Family Bargain Center
  - Signing of North Atlantic Pact, 04/04/1949; wsyr_radio_359; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Signing of North Atlantic Pact; Greek interview, 03/30/1949; 04/04/1949; wsyr_radio_360; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Songs for a soldier (Ripley); President Roosevelt - Youth talk (part 1), 09/02/1942; 09/03/1942; wsyr_radio_179; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sounds for All Seasons, Program No. 65-3, wsyr_radio_922; additional information included in box; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 52)
    One Note Samba - Percy Faith; Day by Day - Franck Pourcel; Gentle on My Mind - Ferrante & Teicher; Moment to Moment - Don Tweedy; Alfie - Hugo Montenegro; The First Time Ever (I Saw Your Face) - Ray Conniff Singers; Happy Heart - David Rose; Baby I’m A Want You, Peter Nero; Mr. Bojangles - Andre Kostelanetz; Darling Lili - Living Strings/ Johnny Douglas; Summer Samba, Walter Wanderley; Remind me - Tony Bennett; It’s Too Late - Hollyridge Strings; Alone Again (Naturally) - Ronnie Aldrich; Michelle - Paul Mauriat; By the Time I Get to Phoenix - Mantovani
  - Sounds for All Seasons, Program No. 90-1, X L Caravan Audition, wsyr_radio_923; additional information included in box; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 52)
    Joy - Percy Faith; Speak Softly Love - Sounds of Sunshine; Volare - Tony Mottola; Theme from Shaft - Ferrante and Teicher; Until It’s Time for You to Go - Andy Williams; Wave - Brass Ring; Toxedo Junction - Enoch Light Orchestra; Without You - James Last Chorus; Peanut Vendor - Tommy Garrett; Born Free - Artie Kane; Hurting Each Other - Karen Carpenter; Song Sung Blue - Chet Atkins; Friendship - Frank Chacksfield; Too Beautiful to Last - Engelbert Humperdinck; Theme from A Summer Place - Paul Mauriat; All I Never Need Is You - Bert Kaempfert; The First Time Ever I Saw Your Face - Percy Faith; Give My Regards To Broadway - Stanley Black
  - Sounds for All Seasons, Program No. 91, wsyr_radio_924; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 52)
  - Speaking of Soaps, wsyr_radio_615; syndicated program; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Special Broadcast from Manila - General McArthur [sic] and President [Sergio] Osmena (parts 1 and 2), 02/26/1945; wsyr_radio_262; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Special eye witness story (part 2); Invasion Broadcasts (part 2), 06/07/1944; wsyr_radio_225; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Side 1: outside cut - Ship air battle; Side 2: #1; # 2 Hicks on battle ship (Part 2 of this on 3rd record)
  - Special news broadcast - Casablanca announcement; "One man’s family" (part 1), 01/26/1943; wsyr_radio_213; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Special Thanksgiving Program with President Roosevelt, part 1; Prime Minister Churchill, part 1, 11/26/1942; 11/29/1942; wsyr_radio_014; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 2)
  - Sports Illustrated interview with Keith Morris and Bill Bradley, ESSO Tiger, wsyr_radio_636; 4 cuts; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - State Senator [Arthur H.] Wicks audio from TV speech, 10/20/1952; wsyr_radio_047; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 8)
    A - NBC program New York State Lieutenant Gov. Arthur H. Wicks (audio from TV speech, this is a film soundtrack); B - UNPLAYABLE
  - "Strip Mining" - Tape Response - Representative Patsy T. Mink, 07/14/1974; wsyr_radio_510; note reads, "Response to an editorial?"; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Syracuse bombing (part 1); President Roosevelt (part 1), 07/25/1943; 07/28/1943; wsyr_radio_192; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Syracuse bombing (part 2); President Roosevelt (part 2), 07/25/1943; 07/28/1943; wsyr_radio_193; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Syracuse Saving Bank spots; J. P. Byrne spot, wsyr_radio_637; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Syracuse speaks - Income Tax cut (part 1); President Truman - VJ Proclamation, 03/12/1948; 03/13/1948; wsyr_radio_346; note on label reads: "Used AM 3/13/1948"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Syracuse Symphony Orchestra - "Sway of thy Gentle Wing" Audio Dub for Radio, 01/11/1976; wsyr_radio_535; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 30:00 (Box 18)
  - Syracuse University Archbold Stadium (TV Audio) Special (1978), wsyr_radio_905; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 51)
  - Syracuse University Basketball - Carrier Classic, 12/02/1978; wsyr_radio_476; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Syracuse University Basketball: Syracuse vs. Iona. Carrier Classic, wsyr_radio_591; sticker on box is # 39; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Syracuse University Commencement Broadcast (First Hour), 05/10/1980; wsyr_radio_478; First hour ends w/ Bill Everett hosting the Denny Sullivan Show.; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 60:00 (Box 14)
  - Syracuse University Football; Interviews; "Guideline", 01/18/1976; wsyr_radio_536; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    1: (2) Larry King - S.U. Football, Archbold Stadium, "Buy Season Tickets" Spots; (2) Tim Roscoe - S.U. F’Ball; (1) Bob Avery - S.U. F’Ball; (1) Bill Zanovich [?] - S.U. F’Ball; 2: WSYR news interviews in an extremely noisy room; 3: Rosemary Hawtton - "Guideline" interview - fragment, NBC Radio Feed; 4: "Guideline" 1/18/76 Religious pgm, Rosemary Hawton interview #3 of 4.
  - Syracuse University. Basketball - Carrier Classic - Manley Field House, wsyr_radio_545; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Teenage Sexuality: You Don’t Have to be In Love to Make Love (No. 1157), Jun 1982; wsyr_radio_928; Cut 1: Introduction; Cut 2: Documentary; Syndicated program; includes Cooperative Extension business card in box; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:00 (Box 52)
    Cut 1 - Introduction 0:30; Cut 2: Documentary 28:30
  - Telephone Interview with Bob Witney and Donald Pedder, 08/06/1953; wsyr_radio_042; Donald Pedder is half brother of POW returnee Harold Dunn, released 8/6/1953.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 17)
  - That Wonderful Wild Band from West Genesee, wsyr_radio_910; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:58 (Box 51)
  - The Carrier Takeover Controversy, 10/27/1978; wsyr_radio_551; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:55 (Box 19)
  - The French National Orchestra: Program 1: Rameau - Dutilleux (part 2), 04/04/1959; wsyr_radio_640; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 30:42 (Box 26)
    1 - Jean-Philippe Rameau (1683-1764): First Suite from Dardanus(13:32), The French National Orchestra, under the direction of Jean Martinon; 2 - Henri Dutilleux (1916-): Le Loup (The Wolf) - excerpt,(2:25), The Radio Symphony Orchestra of the FBS, under the direction of Eugene Bigot; 3 - Henri Dutilleux: Symphony (30:21), The French National Orchestra, under the direction of André Cluytens. Overall time: 53:29. Content list is in Program 1, part 1 box.
  - The French National Orchestra: Program 10: Jacques Dupont - Henri Martelli (part 1), 06/06/1959; wsyr_radio_657; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 27:15 (Box 28)
    Jacques Dupont (1906-): Cello Concerto (Navarrianas) (22:47); Andre Navarra, soloist, Jean Martinon, conductor; Henri Martelli (1899-): Second Symphony for Strings (23:30), Manuel Rosenthal, conductor. Overall time: 53:29. Content list is in box.
  - The French National Orchestra: Program 10: Jacques Dupont - Henri Martelli (part 2), 06/06/1959; wsyr_radio_658; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 26:14 (Box 28)
    Jacques Dupont (1906-): Cello Concerto (Navarrianas) (22:47); Andre Navarra, soloist, Jean Martinon, conductor; Henri Martelli (1899-): Second Symphony for Strings (23:30), Manuel Rosenthal, conductor. Overall time: 53:29. Content list is in Program 10, part 1 box.
  - The French National Orchestra: Program 11: Vandelle - Mirouze - Debussy (part 1), 06/13/1959; wsyr_radio_659; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 30:40 (Box 28)
    Romuald Vandelle (1896-): Symphonie Breve, Adagio maestoso, Allegro con spirito, Andante and Presto (18:31), Manuel Rosenthal conducting; Marcel Mrouze (1914-1957): Concerto for Piano and Orchestra (23:51), Henriette Faure, soloist, Manuel Rosenthal conducting; Claude Debussy (1862-1918): Marche Ecossaise (6:40), D. E. Inghelbrecht conducting. Overall time: 53:04. Content list is in box.
  - The French National Orchestra: Program 11: Vandelle - Mirouze - Debussy (part 2), 06/13/1959; wsyr_radio_660; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 22:24 (Box 29)
    Romuald Vandelle (1896-): Symphonie Breve, Adagio maestoso, Allegro con spirito, Andante and Presto (18:31), Manuel Rosenthal conducting; Marcel Mrouze (1914-1957): Concerto for Piano and Orchestra (23:51), Henriette Faure, soloist, Manuel Rosenthal conducting; Claude Debussy (1862-1918): Marche Ecossaise (6:40), D. E. Inghelbrecht conducting. Overall time: 53:04. Content list is in Program 11, part 1 box.
  - The French National Orchestra: Program 12: Poulenc - Delvincourt (part 1), 06/20/1959; wsyr_radio_661; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 26:27 (Box 29)
    Francis Poulenc (1899-): Concert Champetre (24:13), The composer at the piano, D. E. Inghelbrecht conducting; Claude Delvincourt (1888-1954): Bal Venitien, Prelude, Forlane, Passamezzo, Burlesca, Barcarolle, Mauresca, Tarantella (24:37), Eugene Bigot conducting. Overall time: 53:30. Content list is in box.
  - The French National Orchestra: Program 12: Poulenc - Delvincourt (part 2), 06/20/1959; wsyr_radio_662; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 26:59 (Box 29)
    Francis Poulenc (1899-): Concert Champetre (24:13), The composer at the piano, D. E. Inghelbrecht conducting; Claude Delvincourt (1888-1954): Bal Venitien, Prelude, Forlane, Passamezzo, Burlesca, Barcarolle, Mauresca, Tarantella (24:37), Eugene Bigot conducting. Overall time: 53:30. Content list is in Program 12, part 1 box.
  - The French National Orchestra: Program 13: Destouches - Tomasi - Ibert (part 1), 06/27/1959; wsyr_radio_663; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 34:32 (Box 29)
    Andre-Cardinal Destouches (1672-1749): Callirhoé, Symphonic excerpts from ballet-opera: Overture, 1st & 2nd airs for the fauns & Rondo, 1st & 2nd minuets, Warriors’ step, 1st & 2nd passepieds (12:42), Manuel Rosenthal conducting; Henri Tomasi (1901-): Les Lettres de Mon Moulin: Les Trois Messes Basses (Three Low Masses), Le Secret de Maître Cornille (7:11), Andre Girard conducting; Jacques Ibert (1890-): Symphonie Concertante for Oboe & String Orch.: Allegro con moto, Adagio, Allegro brillante (28:22), Jules Goetgheluck, oboe, Eugene Bigot conducting. Overall time: 53:30. Content list is in box.
  - The French National Orchestra: Program 13: Destouches - Tomasi - Ibert (part 2), 06/27/1959; 07/03/1959; wsyr_radio_664; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 29)
    Andre-Cardinal Destouches (1672-1749): Callirhoé, Symphonic excerpts from ballet-opera: Overture, 1st & 2nd airs for the fauns & Rondo, 1st & 2nd minuets, Warriors’ step, 1st & 2nd passepieds (12:42), Manuel Rosenthal conducting; Henri Tomasi (1901-): Les Lettres de Mon Moulin: Les Trois Messes Basses (Three Low Masses), Le Secret de Maître Cornille(7:11), Andre Girard conducting; Jacques Ibert (1890-): Symphonie Concertante for Oboe & String Orch.: Allegro con moto, Adagio, Allegro brillante (28:22), Jules Goetgheluck, oboe, Eugene Bigot conducting. Overall time: 53:30. Content list is in Program 13, part 1 box.
  - The French National Orchestra: Program 2: Debussy - Mihalovici (part 1), 04/11/1959; wsyr_radio_641; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 21:58 (Box 26)
    Claude Debussy (1862-1918): Iberia (Central section of triptych, Images) in three movements: Par les rues et les chemins; Les Parfums de la Nuit; Le Matin d’un jour de Fete (21:58), under the direction of D. E. Inghelbrecht; Marcel Mihalovici: Scenes de Thesee (Scenes from Theseus), Introduction & Lamento, Concertino, Scherso, Intermezzo, Burlesco, Concerto, Epilogue (25:33), under the direction of Jean Fournet. Overall time: 53:23. Content list is in box.
  - The French National Orchestra: Program 2: Debussy - Mihalovici (part 2), 04/11/1959; wsyr_radio_642; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:33 (Box 26)